I think my dad left because he couldn't bear everyone in town thinking he was a thief.
And mom, I bet her not believing him either was really what bothered him the most.
The whole thing made me want to stop trusting people.
I felt like I was being forced to choose sides.
I thought if I hated my mom or my dad, maybe I'd feel better.
Then a few years later, I heard my mom say,
why couldn't I just believe him?
And I knew she was miserable too.
And then, when I heard her say that, I decided to keep on trusting and loving them both.
I realized that if there's one thing I'm really good at, it's believing in people.
途切れない明日も過ぎたって
立ち止まって 振り返って
止めどない今日を嘆きあった
記憶だって 永遠にだって
残らないもんと思い知って
僕はずっとかきむしって
心の隅っこで泣いた
そしてどうかなくさないだよって
後悔した過ぎる日々を
後悔してんだよって
そう言い逃した
もう君
君を待った
僕は待った
途切れない明日も過ぎてって
僕は今日も
かきむしって
忘れない傷をつけてるんだよ
最後世界は
僕は
What the hell?
I just saw Iri go inside.
Then she might be stuck and can't get out.
Hey!
Iri!
Iri! Can you hear me?
We gotta go.
She's heavy.
Hang on. I'll get you out of here.
Crap.
I can't lug her down by myself.
What are you doing?
You manga guys really should hit the gym more often.
Let's hurry before we get barbecued.
Get going out the back.
I got her from here.
Don't get her mixed up in your shit.
Guess I get to be the hero today.
I hope Iri's okay.
How'd that fire start?
Was it an accident or...
The killer?
Wait.
He was trying to kill Iri with that fire.
And he was trying to frame me for it.
That's why she gave me her phone.
So the cops wouldn't find the email.
He knew where she lived.
Maybe he followed her or...
Maybe she knows him.
Whoever he is, he's close.
I'm going to find him.
And with any luck, I'll get to him before the cops catch me.
This is John Koiro.
Make sure you hold your belongings before dis...
Hello?
All right.
Who is this?
Satoru Fujinuma.
If you're who you say you are, then nice to meet you.
I've been expecting your call.
Sure, be glad to.
But not here.
Someplace public.
No, I'm not telling you who I am just yet.
Tomorrow, when we meet.
Because if you're not who you say you are,
then you're the son of a bitch that killed Sachko.
Sit down anywhere.
Oh.
Hey, Satoru.
Over here.
I'm Sawada.
I used to work with your mom at Ishikari TV.
God damn.
You look just like Sachko.
Yeah.
You're her kid.
No doubt about it.
It's him.
I bet you're wondering if you can trust me.
But there's nothing to worry about.
I didn't tell the cops you called,
and I didn't kill your mom.
Yeah, well, maybe you think I killed her.
Not even.
How can you be sure?
Because I knew your mom,
and I know she didn't raise the kind of son who'd kill her.
Hmm, I see.
Yeah, I remembered I had it in my pocket yesterday.
You're in it deep, that's for sure.
Tell me about it.
And now I'm on the run because I panicked.
I can't stop screwing things up.
What happened, happened, so it's pointless to beat yourself up about it.
Huh?
That's something your mom liked to say.
It's kind of appropriate, don't you think?
You want me to tell you what we talked about the other day?
Yeah.
Do you remember 18 years ago, when that serial killer was targeting kids?
Yeah, sure.
Jun Shiratori's still sitting on death row and still denying he killed him.
Well, Satoru was right about him.
Huh?
Shiratori's innocent.
And I think I figured out who the real killer is.
Can you meet me at Koiwa Station tomorrow?
I should have asked for the guy's name.
Anyway, let's talk about what happened back then.
About how Kayo Hinazuki died.
We know that on the night of March the 2nd,
Kayo's mom and her boyfriend beat her and locked her in the shed.
That was around 10, and she was still alive.
We know she froze to death.
And we also know that when the mom and the boyfriend found her body the next morning,
they hid it, because they didn't want to take the fall for the murder.
But I'm getting ahead of myself.
The theory goes that Kayo was taken from the shed sometime after 10 p.m.
At about 12.30, Kayo's mom went out to get her and found her gone.
Then she called your house and asked your mom if she knew where Kayo was.
When they arrested Jun Shiratori,
the only evidence they had that tied him to the crime was a pair of rubber boots he owned.
The tread matched tracks they found near the shed.
Here's how the police figured the killing went down.
First, he knocked her out and took some pictures of her.
Next, he put her in the walk-in freezer at work and sprayed her with water.
As soon as her temperature dropped to 20 degrees, she was brain dead.
He waited around for about 30 minutes to make sure she was gone.
Then, just before dawn, he put her body back in the shed.
There's no way Yuki killed her.
Kayo Hinazuki, Hiromi Sugita, and Aya Nakanishi.
Just before those three went missing,
the same exact thing happened in the next town over from yours.
Someone was quickly arrested,
but he swore he was innocent, same as Shiratori.
You see?
Same crime, same pattern.
It's beyond coincidental.
That means...
Exactly.
I've been trying to tell people for years.
They called me crazy, but in the end I was right.
These crimes were never really solved.
The killer framed every suspect.
So whoever murdered Kayo also murdered Sachiko.
He's still on the loose.
In this city?
This bastard's beyond clever.
He plants a false trail of evidence at the scene of the crime
that leads the cops away from him
and straight towards some other poor sucker.
And while everyone looks the other way,
he kills again.
This is too much.
You think you'll try it again?
If Fujinuma shows his face here,
I'm gonna take his ass out personally.
So what's the story with the high school girl?
She was in it with him.
Yeah, but he didn't want any loose threads,
so he tried to kill her too to shut her up.
Dragging her into the shit.
What an asshole.
They're wrong.
Please, Irie.
You don't have to apologize for anything.
Your uncle's right.
We didn't know there was a stalker after you.
You must have been so terrified.
But, Auntie, that's not...
You poor thing.
We shouldn't have left you all alone in the house like that.
You're wrong.
The police know who it is,
and they'll catch him soon.
You have nothing to worry about now.
They're all wrong.
Everyone thinks Satoru killed his mom and tried to kill me.
But that's crazy.
It doesn't matter what I say.
No one believes me.
You sure the message was sent from Sachko's phone?
Yeah.
Before I could get Irie out of the house,
she slipped her phone in my pocket.
Check it out.
You weren't kidding.
Looks like he wanted to help the cops catch you
by pinning the fire on you, too.
But why go to all that trouble?
I'm already a suspect in one murder.
Uh-uh.
This wasn't about framing me.
He was after Irie for another reason.
Do you think he tried to kill her
because she had something on him?
To get me to take the fall for my mom's murder,
he had to know when I'd be home to find her.
That means he knew my schedule.
So in the 24 hours between when my mom saw him
try to kidnap that little girl,
and when he killed my mom,
he must have gone to the pizza place
and had a look at the shift schedule.
If that's what happened,
I bet Irie saw his face.
He might even be someone I've seen before.
It's possible.
All we have to do is find out
who got behind the counter that day,
and we might have our killer.
Hell, it's worth a shot.
It might even break this case wide open.
I'm off to the hospital.
Uh, okay.
There's a report on the murders
from 18 years ago on my computer.
You should check it out.
I have a theory that Jun Shiratori
might suspect his father to be the killer.
Shiratori's refusal to talk to authorities
did not help his case.
Perhaps he did not want to say anything
that could possibly incriminate his father.
That figures.
Yuki loved his dad.
Kayo Hinazuki's classmates testified
they had seen her and Shiratori together many times.
The investigators focused on their testimonies
while ignoring Satoru Fujinuma's.
Suspects.
I don't know any of them besides Yuki and his dad.
They only had five?
The investigators thought Hiromi Sugita was murdered
because the killer mistook him for a girl.
Based on this assumption,
they made a list of five suspects,
none of whom knew Hiromi Sugita.
He eat today as folk dancing.
Ew, that sucks ass.
I don't want to hold some ugly girl's hand,
but I'd be okay holding Hiromi's.
Oh, that's butsy.
I think I know why Hiromi was murdered.
The killer knew he was a boy.
He only killed him to cover his tracks.
To keep his name off the list.
Jun Shiratori was arrested
after someone in the neighborhood
reported seeing him talking to a third grade girl.
The girl was alone at the time.
In the storage room of Shiratori Foods,
police found photos of Hiromi Sugita's body.
In these photos,
investigators suspected Jun Shiratori
of having pedophiliac tendencies,
and magazines popular with pedophiles
were found in his room,
confirming their suspicions.
He didn't have that shit.
The killer planted that stuff
to keep the cops off his trail.
Who were the suspects before Hiromi died?
Tanda won the killer's names on it.
Miss Katagiri, are you awake?
Excuse me, I'm visiting someone,
but is the bathroom that way?
Yes.
Her name wouldn't be listed.
201's vacant.
That's it.
She's sound asleep.
Thanks for the update.
Oh, one side!
I gotta pee like a mother!
Miss Katagiri,
sorry to barge in on you like this.
You wouldn't happen to be Satoru Fujinuma, hmm?
No, actually I'm a friend of Satoru's.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Iri's mother.
Satoru didn't do what the police are saying.
I know he didn't kill his mom,
and he wasn't trying to kill me either.
He didn't set that fire.
He was the one who saved me from it.
You're confused.
After breathing all that smoke,
your manager got you out of the house in time.
I don't know what they've told you,
but none of it's true.
They're even saying I helped him kill his mom.
The worst part about all this is,
no one believes me.
No one believes Satoru either,
and he's all alone now.
Iri,
even after all these years,
I still think about your father.
I should have gone after him.
I believe you, hun.
Hurry up now.
Go and find Satoru.
Oh, crap.
I forgot to turn it off.
You left it on.
Thank God.
Iri,
are you okay?
Oh, yeah.
I'm good as new,
but I need to see you.
Can you meet me under the you-know-what?
Wait.
No, don't go there.
I got you in enough trouble as...
Don't worry.
I'll make sure no one follows me.
Promise.
And go!
Yeah!
Let's follow it!
Meeting her isn't a good idea.
I could have asked if she saw someone
peeking at the schedule.
The more she gets involved,
the worse it's gonna be for her.
That sucked.
It didn't fly that far at all.
Yeah, how come?
The wings are straight.
If you do this,
it'll give it more aerodynamic lift.
Are you sure that's really gonna help it?
Try it out.
No way!
It worked!
Look!
It's heading for the river!
What's a grown-up doing here
at this time of day?
Is he out of work?
I hope he's not a pervert.
Poor Yuki.
I bet he had to hear
the same thing back then.
What do you do if he hits this way?
I'm sorry.
Ok.
Have I been there?
I don't know.
Where did he come on?
OK.
I didn't know about it.
Well...
Why let's human pages fail given to me.
But first I'll come back to you.
And that...
go wherever I come on,
give me Tità one time to notice.
Give me väldigt Thomas
and my family...
institutional calls to him
to family,
whether I've been somewhere
See? I made it.
Yeah.
And I made sure no one followed, like I promised.
Cool. I feel terrible. For a sec there, I thought this might be a trap by the cops. I said that out loud.
You better be thinking like that. You're a fugitive, so you can't take any chances.
Anyway, I'm glad you trusted me enough to meet me.
Yeah.
At work? I'd say Mr. Nishizono's pretty sketchy.
Nishizono?
I've seen him once or twice. He's on the city council because he wears that pin.
The boss is always kissing his butt, too.
When they meet, it's always been in the boss's office.
So he could totally peek at the schedule and get my address.
Heck, I even said hi to him.
The list didn't have a Nishizono on it. Maybe it's a fake name.
No, he couldn't use a fake name if he's on the city council.
I think he came after me because I saw his face before.
It's not coming together. God damn it. There's still a piece missing.
Satoru? I know how you must be feeling, but you can't beat yourself up.
I try and try. I can never make things right.
Oh, nothing. It's an idea for a manga I had.
The Grim Reaper makes a scheduling error and a kid dies on the wrong day.
He tries to bring the kid back to life, but it backfires.
Someone else dies, so he tries again.
And someone else suffers.
He just wants to do the right thing, but everyone he meets ends up one way or the other.
Miserable or dead.
So are you saying you're kind of like that Grim Reaper?
Yeah, that's exactly what I'm saying.
You're an idiot.
Do I look dead?
And as for being miserable or whatever, what does he know?
That's his opinion.
Your Grim Reaper character should have a little more faith in himself.
I think it's too soon to give up on what you want because nothing's set in stone.
However, this inn's still up in the air, and no one knows what it's going to be yet.
Iri, I'm really glad I got to meet you.
I said that out loud.
Satoru Fujinuma?
Run, Satoru!
Out of the way!
Iri!
Satoru Fujinuma, you're under arrest for murder.
Attempted murder and arson.
4.50pm.
Suspect apprehended.
He didn't do it!
Let me go!
He's innocent!
He didn't kill anyone!
Satoru!
I knew me and Iri wouldn't last.
Either I'd get caught or Revival would make it disappear.
Here it is.
The last time I'll ever see her.
I know what I should do.
Satoru!
I'm sorry!
I didn't tell if you were here!
I swear I didn't tell!
They fall at me!
I'm sorry, Satoru!
I have to leave her with some kind of hope.
Just like she did for me.
I'm sorry!
Is this all my fault?
What would a superhero say at a time like this?
Isn't it hard having to fight bad guys by yourself?
It's not your fault.
I know I'll get through this somehow.
Because I know you believe in me.
So thank you, Iri.
I'm glad I trusted you.
I told you.
Let's be nervous.
You didn't miss out.
I'm sorry.
I like it.
I don't like the race.
You're not thedelicats.
Bye.
Then I'll keep you in, tips for now.
H
be honest
it's as subtle
to my admit
when I am born
I will come back with you
I want you to keep you
below´s the change
if I remember
I am waiting for you
between me
二人を隠したこの街に誰も知らない雪が降っていた
君は僕の胸に刻まれた一番深いキス跡のようで
君が笑うこの世界の歌
鳴り戻すよ